(Sheldon:)Or just my normal look
of haughty derision?
(Raj:)-You don't know we're wrong yet.
-Haughty derision it is.
(Amy:)Excuse me. I'm Amy Farrah Fowler.
You're Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry to inform you
that you have been taken in...
(Sheldon:)...by unsupportable mathematics...
(Sheldon:)...designed to prey
on the gullible and the lonely.
(Sheldon:)Additionally, I'm being blackmailed
with a hidden dirty sock.
(Amy:)If that was slang, I'm unfamiliar with it.
(Amy:)If it was literal,
I share your aversion to soiled hosiery.
(Amy:)I'm here because my mother and I have
agreed that I will date at least once a year.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Amy:)My mother and I have
the same agreement about church.
(Amy:)I don't object to the concept of a deity,
but I'm baffled by the notion...
(Amy:)...of one that takes attendance.
(Sheldon:)Well, then you might
want to avoid East Texas.
(Amy:)Noted. Now, before this goes any further,
you should know...
(Amy:)...that all forms of physical contact
up to and including coitus are off the table.
(Sheldon:)May I buy you a beverage?
(Amy:)Tepid water, please.
(Howard:)Good God, what have we done?